logoarena.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy policy | Logo Arena

## Privacy policy

The privacy of our community is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by us and how it is used. We will protect personal information by using security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.

Any personal information collected will not be disclosed, shared or sold to any third party other than Logo Arena's sister concerns (companies that are operated under a single corporation) which fall within same user segments (i.e. graphic designing). We reserve the right to modify current privacy policy at our own discretion.

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, we make use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that may lead to a user's identity.

## Private messages (PM) and private contest discussions

Clients and designers can communicate with each other via private messages and private contest discussion boards. Members' private messages and contest discussions are hidden from the general community.

## Cookies

Cookies are very small text fles that are stored on your computer device when you use it to visit many websites. We use cookies to distinguish you from other users, by tracking visitor behaviour and storing certain site preferences. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you use or browse the website and also allows us to improve our products, services and the website.

If you prefer not to allow the use of cookies, you can change the confguration of your browser to either warn you when you receive a cookie or to automatically reject them. However, you may find that disabling cookies means that certain areas of our site do not function correctly.

## What types of cookies do we use?

**Session cookies** – A session cookie remembers your login for you and what you have put in your shopping basket. We consider these to be strictly necessary for the working of our website. If these are disabled, then various functions on our site will not work.

**Google Analytics** \- We use this tool to understand how the website is being used so as to improve user experience. The user data is anonymous.

**Google Remarketing** – Google uses these cookies to show relevant adverts to users who have previously visited our site, as they browse other websites. To opt-out from Google's remarketing programme, please edit your Google Ad Settings.

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads), and if you want to you can Opt Out of Interest-Based Advertising visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) page.

**Facebook** – Cookies and pixels are used to understand and deliver ads and make them more relevant to you. We may also use a cookie to learn whether someone who saw an advert on Facebook later visited our website.

Facebook is able to connect the data with your Facebook account and use them for their own advertising purposes, in accordance with Facebook's Data Use Policy found at: https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/. Facebook conversion tracking also allows Facebook and its partners to show you advertisements on and outside Facebook. In addition, a cookie will be saved onto your computer for these purposes. Please [click here](https://www.facebook.com/ads/website_custom_audiences) if you would like to revoke your permission.

By registering with Logo Arena, you hereby acknowledge and agree to the above privacy policy and any amendments to it hence forth.

For further information or concerns about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us via email at [info@logoarena.com](mailto:info@logoarena.com).
